I believe very many in high school anyway in the beginning it takes for granted
And it looks a bit more like elementary school.
But high school plays quite a lot of role how far you come in.
It was like "either I plug in finance or law".
Since I had a greater interest in law, I chose to plug it instead.
I knew that the law program is a program that has high admission points.
So it was a motivation when I read in high school to study hard.
Then I did not plug all the time, you have your periods when it goes up and down.
During high school, that thought process was what one wanted to become and
Rights and check out a little at universities, it might get started in second.
At the end of the second and more in the third to first year in high school
But examples like economics, there is a lot you can do afterwards.
Just.
It took five years for me before I even knew I wanted to start plugging really.
When you go back to high school when choosing programs
I felt that I didn't know if I wanted to go on after that.
I was a little tired of school.
I was a little defiant teenager if you say so.
And then I started looking around a bit at what was there.
And realized that I still want the options open.
I didn't want to choose one
vocational preparation without a study preparation.
So after the student I started working.
And continued to work and have been out and traveled some.
It is also a student city.
It is quite difficult to get hold of accommodation but it is a little easier here.
One thing with Örebro University is that it is a comprehensive campus.
Exactly.
All buildings are in the same place.
Teachers, economists, rhetoricians.
Everyone is really together.
Then in some buildings you have the most lessons in.
So it gets a little divided that way.
But unlike some other cities, it will not be scattered.
With a building being in one side of the city
And the other in the other side of town.